Ashish Kumar Singh

GeeksForGeeks | LinkedIn | GitHub | Leetcode Email: ashishsinghk2020@gmail.com | Mobile:7302433809

GAME DEVELOPER

Working as a Game Developer with Ingenuity Gaming Pvt Ltd since Oct 2021 in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and TypeScript. I have knowledge of popular frameworks and libraries such as Quest, PIXI.js, React and experience with MVC frameworks.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : JavaScript, TypeScript, C++, HTML,

Frameworks : Quest, Reactjs, Tailwind Libraries : PIXI.js, STL,Phaser

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git, Gitlab

EXPERIENCE

DS Daikokuten Game

Oct 2022 - Present

Ingenuity Gaming Pvt. Ltd.

- Developed this Game for a very famous client, named JadeBat using (JavaScript, Reactjs and PIXI.js)
- Worked on developing features in this game using React, JS, PIXI and also developed the complete UI through our Internal Framework QUEST
- · Improved Game performance and speed through Assets and Animation optimization techniques by 30%

Game Lobby

July 2021 - Sep 2022

Ingenuity Gaming Pvt. Ltd.

- · Worked with React to develop Different components for client's Game Lobby
- Developed Highly responsive user interface, fixed bugs and issues in the frontEnd to ensure beautiful
 UI of the Game Lobby

EDUCATION

Galgotias University

Greater Noida, UP

Bachelor of Computer Science And Engineering (7.6 CGPA)

July 2018 - July 2022

PROJECTS

Swiggy Clone

React. js, HTML, CSS, JS, Git

Source Code

- Build a Swiggy Clone using React.js using Swiggy API
- · Implemented functionalities to search for food and placed the order.Implemented the cart functionality using redux

YouTube Clone

React. js, HTML, CSS, JS, Git

Source Code

- . Build a YouTube Clone using Reactjs using YouTube Open APIs.
- .Implemented functionalities to search using Debouncing, n-level commenting, Live chat functionality

CERTIFICATIONS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

- Won High-Roller Award(Top Performer of the Studio Individual)
- Won Prime Team Award(Best team of the Studio Team)